AHMAD SYAIKHAN

JUNIOR POSITION

CONTACT

+6

+6018 406 2747

 \boxtimes

syaikhan.work@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmadsyaikhan-mat-desa-74a7a3258/



Johor, Malaysia Selangor, Malaysia

SKILLS

Programming - Flutter, Codelgniter3 Laravel, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, Java, Python, MySQL

Data Analytics - PowerBI, Tableau, Excel

UI/UX Design using Figma

Office Applications & Computer Software and Hardware repair/troubleshoot

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Information Systems Engineering

UiTM Jasin, Melaka

2020-2023

- Graduate with 3.35 CGPA
- Members of ISEC (Information Systems Engineering Club)

REFERENCES

Othman Irfan Bin Abu Bakar

IT Executives at Rexpocentral Sdn Bhd +6019 716 9910

Zakwan Karim

Senior colleague at GWIP Sdn Bhd +60 11-3667 3524

LANGUAGES

Malay English

PROFILE

A young and energetic professional with strong English communication skills and a passion for technology. I have 2 years of hands-on experience in web and mobile app development, specializing in backend development using Codelgniter3 and Laravel, with occasional involvement in frontend implementation. I've worked with .NET and Laravel for web solutions, and developed cross-platform mobile applications using Flutter. My interests extend to UI/UX design, IoT, routing protocols, software development and data analytics. Eager to explore new opportunities where I can further apply and grow my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Apps Developer - Fulltime (Flutter, Codelgniter3, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

GWIP Sdn. Bhd.

May 2024 - Present

- Developed and maintained cross-platform mobile applications using Flutter for Android
- Designed and built RESTful APIs using PHP Codelgniter 3 framework to support mobile app backends.
- Managed and structured databases using MySQL, interfaced via phpMyAdmin.
- Collaborated with team members to deliver multiple functional apps across various departments within the company.
- Heavily involved in most of projects that requires backend development.

Software Engineer - Fulltime (asp.NET Core, C#, MySQL) SATO Auto-ID Malaysia Sdn. Bhd. August 2023 - February 2024

Systems Enhancement Support for KONICA Fixed Asset Data Collection System (FADCS):

- Worked on improving the KONICA Fixed Asset Data Collection System using ASP.NET Core, Javascript, and Microsoft SQL Server.
- Tested the system thoroughly and trained users at their location.

Systems Enhancement for FITLINE Event Management Systems using Label Issuing Systems (LIS):

- Improved FITLINE's event management systems by integrating Label Issuing Systems.
- Collaborated with teams to make systems better and easier to use.

Systems Enhancement and Support of YukTung Properties Asset Tracking Systems (ATS):

- Improved YukTung Properties Asset Tracking Systems according to their requirements and specifications.
- Designed labels for their assets tagging and made the system more userfriendly.

Software Developer - Internship

H-Drones & Robotics Sdn. Bhd.

March 2023 - July 2023

- Responsible for producing an interactive UI/UX for their Artificial Intelligence Gate (AIG) software project for Honda Service Center using Figma.
- Backend support for AIG project; support main programmer using python.
- Frontend support for KartHauz mobile apps. Developed using Flutter.
- Perform mapping of an area using drone via DroneDeploy apps. Drone model used is Mavic 2.